Guide to the Charles Downing Lay papers, 1898-1956
Lay, Charles Downing papers, 1898-1956
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Charles Downing Lay papers, 1898-1956.
4477
Charles Downing Lay 1877-1956.
11 cubic ft., 12 Map case folders
Notebooks, papers, correspondence, photographs, drawings.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Notebooks of architectural class notes and drawings; student papers; notebooks and sketchbooks on gardens; photographs of gardens and parks; architectural drawings and renderings; pen and ink drawings; and articles on architectural topics.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Landscape architect, architect, town planner.
Charles Downing Lay attended the School of Architecture at Columbia University from 1896 to 1900 and received a S.B. in Landscape Architecture from Harvard University's School of Landscape Architecture in 1902. From 1902 to 1948 he maintained a landscape architecture practice in New York City. He served as editor and publisher of Landscape Architecture with H. V. Hubbard and Robert Wheelwright. His projects included town planning for Albany, N.Y. and for the United States Housing Corporation in Erie and Butler, Pa.; parks in New York City, Troy, Albany, Schenectady, and Brooklyn, N.Y., Washington, D.C., and Stratford, Connecticut; school grounds in New York, Massachusetts, and Connecticut; subdivisions in New York, Massachusetts, Rhode Island, Connecticut, and New Jersey; and housing in New York City. He also was consulting architect to the 1939 New York World's Fair and worked on conservation efforts in the Housatonic River valley, founding the Housatonic Valley Planning Association in 1948.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Notebooks of architectural class notes and drawings, 1898, 1899; student papers; notebooks and sketchbooks on gardens; photographs of gardens and parks, especially Marine Park in Brooklyn; architectural drawings and renderings; pen and ink drawings; and articles on architectural topics. Also, papers relating to lectures; and club memberships, including the Century Club; miscellaneous correspondence; and condolence letters upon his death.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Lay, Charles Downing,1877-1956.; Housatonic Valley Planning Association.; United States Housing Corporation.; New York World's Fair (1939-1940)
Titles:
Landscape architecture.
Subjects:
Landscape architecture.; City planning--New York (N.Y.); City planning--Pennsylvania--Erie.; City planning--Pennsylvania--Butler.; School grounds--New York (State); School grounds--Washington (D.C.); School grounds--Connecticut--Stratford.; Housing development--New York (State); Housing development--Rhode Island.; Housing development--Connecticut.; Housing development--New Jersey.; Housing--New York (N.Y.); Gardens--Design.; Landscape architects.; Architects and housing developers.
Places:
Marine Park (New York, N.Y.)
Form and Genre Terms:
Architectural drawings.; Photographs.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
PUBLIC AREAS INCLUDED IN THE COLLECTION
Battery Park
Beaver Park, Albany, NY
Bridgford Park, Albany, NY
Butler, Pennsylvania
Cemetary of the Gate of Heaven, Mount Pleasant, NY
Central Park (A. Mitchell Memorial) New York City
Coney Island (New York City Fair) 1943
(Old) Essex County Golf Course, East Orange, New Jersey
Erie, Pennsylvania
Frear Park, Troy, New York
Loudon Heights, Albany, New York
Madison Square, New York City
Marine Park
North End Junior High School, Stratford, Connecticut
Overview Park, Pittsfield, Massachusetts
Philips Gallery, Washington, D.C.
Prospect Park, New York City
Recreation Terraces and Public Baths, New York City
Ridgefield Public School, Ridgefield, Connecticut
Rock Spring Country Club
St. Nicholas Houses, Manhattan, New York
Salem, Massachusetts
Seaside Park, Westbrook, Connecticut
Schenectady, New York
Sheepshead Bay Houses, Brooklyn, New York City
Stratford, Connecticut War Memorial and other
Tompkins Square, New York
Verona Civic Center, Verona, New Jersey
Washington Square
(Property of) Wheaton, Illinois
Woodruff Park, Stratford, Connecticut
PRIVATE ESTATES INCLUDED IN THE COLLECTION
Elbridge L. Adams, Great Barrington, Massachusetts
George B. Agnew, Lewisboro, New York
Robert C. Anderson, Upper Montclair, New Jersey
J. Charles Andrews, Great Neck, Long Island
J. Percy Bartram, Caritas Island, Stamford, Connecticut
Edgar Bassick, Bridgeport, Connecticut
Mrs. Edgar W. Bassick, Fairfield, Connecticut
A. Bijur, Long Branch, New Jersey
Mrs. H. S. Bowen/Belton Farms, Round Hill, Greenwich, Connecticut
Thomas Bowen and J. Moss Ives, Mattapan, Locust Valley, Long Island
Gilbert C. Brown
Thomas W. Bryant, Torrington, Connecticut
A. P. Budd, Brewster, New York
Anson W. Burchard, Locust Valley, Long Island
E. A. Cappleen
Casagmo, Ridgefield, Connecticut
J. P. Chamberlain, Waterbury and Middlebury, Connecticut
K. F. Cooper, Great Neck, Long Island
John O'Hara Cosgrave, Stamford, Connecticut
Don W. Murray Crane, Dalton, Massachusetts
W. M. Crane, Jr., Dalton, Massachusetts
Mrs. Z. M. Crane, Dalton, Massachusetts
Walter H. Crittenden
John W. Davis, Locust Valley, Long Island
Mrs. W. B. Devreux, Jr., Syosset, Long Island
Dodge
W. A. Donald, South Yarmouth, Massachusetts
A. W. Eaton, Pittsfield, Massachusetts
Florham
Harold Forsberg, Stratford, Connecticut
A. A. Fowler, Peapack, New Jersey
S. Miller Gallaher, Charleston, West Virginia
Gill
Miss Grata Hostetter, Locust Valley, Long Island
Miss Bertha M. Howland
Mr. & Mrs. Jerome C. Hunsaker, Brookville, Long Island
J. Percy Keating, St. Martins, Pennsylvania
Kraushaar
S. Forry Laucks, York County, Pennsylvania
Edwin Lefevre, Dorset, Vermont
H. H. Lehman, Harrison, New York
Robert Scott Lovett
Charles W. McAlpin
R. L. McIntosh, Westfield, Connecticut
C. A. Mallory, Danbur, Connecticut
George O. May, Fairfield, Connecticut
Mitchell Memorial
Mr. and Mrs. Edward Mogul, Easton, Connecticut
E. B. Morris, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania
Mr. & Mrs. Winchester Noyes, Huntington, Long Island
George M. Olcott, Ridgefield, Connecticut
G. Pagenstecher, Storm King, New York
Andrew J. Post, Sound Beach, Old Greenwich, Connecticut
Charles W. Power, Pittsfield, Massachusetts
Pratt Mausoleum, Glen Cove, Long Island
Sherburne Prescott, Greenwich, Connecticut
Ralph Pulitzer, Manhasset, Long Island
Roberts
Seift
Sheldon
William A. Siewers, White Plains, New York
R. H. Simpson, Oyster Bay, New York
L. A. Cappelan Smith, ___ Point, Long Island
Edgar Stillman
George J. Stockley, Great Neck, Long Island
A. S. Storer, Ridgefield, Connecticut
Mrs. Lyman Beecher Stowe, Forest Hills Gardens, Long Island
Walker E. Swift, Norton, Connecticut
T. L. Van Norden, South Salem, New York
Mr. & Mrs. Alexander Van Rensselaer, Fort Washington, Pennsylvania
Annie Vietor [Victor?] Rumson
Maurice Wertheim, Cos Cob, Connecticut
James M. Willcox, Radnor, Pennsylvania
Mrs. Willis D. Wood, Huntington, Long Island
Charles Yarnall, Newton Square, Pennsylvania
William Zinsser, Great Neck, Long Island
RELATED MATERIALS
Related collections: Oliver Ingraham Lay, Charles Downing Lay, and Lay family papers at the Archives of American Art, https://www.aaa.si.edu/collections/oliver-ingraham-lay-charles-downing-lay-and-lay-family-papers-6011.
SERIES LIST
Series I. Personal
Box 1, Folders 1-4; Box 18, Folder 1; Box 19
Series II. Student Papers
Box 1, Folders 5-14
Series III. Correspondence
Box 1, Folders 15-39; Box 18, Folder 5-6
Series IV. Art and Artists
Box 1, Folders 40-56
Series V. Private Homes and Estates
Box 1, Folders 57-68
Series VI. Architecture, Planning, etc.: Housing, Parks, Committees and Other
Box 2, Folders 1-49
Series VII. Writings
Box 2, Folder 50 - Box 3, Folder 22; Box 18, Folder 10
Series VIII. Printed Material
Boxes 4-7
Series IX. Photographs and negatives of private homes, estates, public areas and other
Boxes 8-17
Series X. Oversize blueprints, sketches, drawings, paintings and photographs
Box 19; Mapcase Folder 1-13
Series XI. Other
Box 18, Folder 2, 3, 4, 7, 8, 9
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. Personal
  - Obituaries (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Bibliography (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Copies of holograph list of paintings of Oliver I. Lay II (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Letter written by Laura Lay to Women’s Committee, Emergency Peace Federation, 1917 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Condolence letters, 1940-1956 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Job photograph album (Cambridge, Storer, Van Norden), 1930 (Box 19)
  - Scrapbook newspaper clippings, 1924-1933 (Box 19)
- Series II. Student Papers
  - The Back Bay Fens, Boston, Massachusetts, 1901 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - The Gardens of Haddon Hall, Dec. 21, 1900 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - The Gore Place - Waltham (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Horticulture I (Box 1, Folder 7-9)
  - Horticulture II (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Prospect Park, Brooklyn - 3rd class, L.L.S. (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Reports, October 12, 1900 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Trees and Shrubs (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - The Tuscan Order (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Series III. Correspondence, 1900-1956
  - A (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - B (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - C (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - D (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Darling, J. N. (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - E (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - F (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - G (including "Gorge") (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - H (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - J-K (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - L (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Lahey, Charles (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - M (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - N-O (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - P (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - R (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - S (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Speicher, Eugene (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - T-V (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - W (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Y-Z (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Condolence letters, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Unknown (no last name or illegible) (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - European trip account to Mr. Thomas(includes travel miscellany), 1934 (Box 1, Folder 38-39)
  - Misc. correspondence, 1940-1947 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Harvard correspondence, 1900-1902 (Box 18, Folder 6)
- Series IV. Art and Artists
  - A (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - B (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - C (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - D (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - E-F (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - G (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - H (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - I-K (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - L (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - M (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - N (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - P (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - R (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - S (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - T-U (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - W (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Z (Box 1, Folder 56)
- Series V. Private Homes and Estates
  - Adams, Elbridge L., Great Barrington, Massachusetts (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Agnew, George B., Lewisboro, New York (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Bartram, J. Percy, Caritas Island, Stamford, Connecticut (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Bowen, Mrs. H. S., Greenwich, Connecticut (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Chamberlain, Joseph, Middlebury, Connecticut (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - McAlpin, Charles W., Morristown, New Jersey (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - May, George O., Southport, Connecticut (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Mogull, Edward, Easton, Connecticut (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Morse, E. B., Philadelphia, Pennsylvania (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Stillman, Edgar, Middlebury, Connecticut (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Willcox, James M., Radnor, Pennsylvania (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - Miscellaneous details, plans (Box 1, Folder 68)
- Series VI. Architecture, Planning, etc.: Housing, Parks, Committees and Other
  - American Institute of Architects (A.I.A.) Civic Design Committee, 1942-1948 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - A.I.A. New York Chapter, 1934-1953 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Arnold Arboretum, 1954-1955 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Art Commission - New York, 1949-1952 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Art Students' League of New York, 1931-1936 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Battery-Brooklyn Bridge, 1939 (Box 2, Folder 6-7)
  - The Brooklyn Daily Eagle - Brooklyn Committee on the City Plan, 1914 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Central Park - miscellaneous extracts, 1911 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Coney Island, 1942-1945 (Box 2, Folder 10-11)
  - East Harlem, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Greenwich, Connecticut, 1942 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Housatonic Valley Planning Association records, 1939-1972 (Box 2, Folder 14-22)
  - Long Island Parks, 1925 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Long Island State Park Commission, 1925 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Marine Park, 1932 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Nassau County Committee, 1925 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Natural Resources Council - Connecticut, 1951-1954 (Box 2, Folder 27-28)
  - Neustadter Foundation, Yonkers, 1949-1950 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - New York City, 1908 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - New York City, 1919 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - New York City Park Department, 1913 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - New York City Parks, 1927-1934 (Box 2, Folder 33-34)
  - New York City Planning Commission, 1938-1940 (Box 2, Folder 35-37)
  - New York Recreation Terrace, 1927 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - New York City - Vehicular Traffic Committee, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - New York City War Memorial, 1923 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - New York World's Fair, 1939 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - New York World's Fair - Gardens on Parade (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - 1938 Olympic Award - Marine Park, 1936-1947 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - St. Nicholas Houses - New York City Housing Authority, 1952-1955 (Box 2, Folder 44-45)
  - Sharon, Connecticut (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Scintilla-Bendix, Sidney, New York (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Sterling Park, Stratford, Connecticut, 1935-1937 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Washington Square (Box 2, Folder 49)
- Series VII. Writings
  - List of Writings (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Conservation (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Farming (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Forest and Trees (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - "Freedom of the City;" "Garden Book of Autumn and Winter," Duffield & Co., 1917-1933 (Box 2, Folder 54)
    Writings related to the works, not the works themselves
  - Gardens - Chapter V (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Housing (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Land and Outdoors (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - The Loon and the Vesper (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Nassau County, 1925 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - New York Times Article (Box 2, Folder 60-61)
  - Outdoor Delights, Chapter VII (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - A Park System for Long Island, 1925 (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Planning the Country Club Grounds, 1930 (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - A Tame Crow - Woodshed (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Published magazine articles (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous writings (Box 3, Folder 2-22)
  - Unpublished manuscript, Undated (Box 18, Folder 10)
- Series VIII. Printed Material
  - Public Parks, Frederick Law Olmsted, 1902 (Box 4)
  - Hudson Nurseries, Inc., 1929 (Box 4)
  - State of Connecticut Report of the State Park Commission, 1914 (Box 4)
  - Landscape Architecture compiled index, 1910-1930 (Box 4)
  - Landscape Architecture, April 1958 and 1965 (Box 4)
  - Notes on Preparation of Contracts and Specifications, by Albert D. Taylor, 1927 (Box 4)
  - The Prairie Spirit in Landscape Gardening, Illinois Agricultural Experiment Station, November 1915 (Box 4)
  - The Future of Jamaica Bay, Department of Parks, New York City, 1938 (Box 4)
  - Journal of the Society of Architectural Historians, May 1956 (Box 4)
  - Beauty in Gardens - A Tribute, William Edwin Rudge, 1928 (Box 4)
- Series IX. Photographs and negatives of private homes, estates, public areas and other
  - Glass lantern slides: New York City parks including Central, Prospect, and Coney Island; private homes and estates; housing projects, other parks. (Box 5-7)
  - Small - in alphabetical order (Box 8)
  - Adams (Box 9, Folder 1-2)
  - Agnew (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Albany - evergreens Ravine Beaver park (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Art Commission of the City of New York (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Bartram (Box 9, Folder 6-7)
  - Battery-Brooklyn Bridge (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Bowen (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Bryant (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Cappleen (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Crittenden (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Donald (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Eaton (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Essex Country Golf Course (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - France (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Frear park (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Philips Gallery (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Greenburgh, New York (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Hunsaker (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Laucks (Box 9, Folder 21-24)
  - Lefevre (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Long Island parks (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Lovett (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - McAlpin (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Mallory (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Marine Park (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 9, Folder 31-33)
  - Morris (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Nassau County Committee (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - National Academy of Sciences Washington, D.C. (Box 10, Folder 3-4)
  - New York City (Box 10, Folder 5-6)
  - New York City Park Department (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - New York City Parks (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - New York Recreation Terrace (Box 10, Folder 9-10)
  - New York Training School, Cortland, New York (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - New York World's Fair, 1939 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Power (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Olcott (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Post (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Pratt - mausoleum (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Pulitzer (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Roberts (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Salem, Massachusetts (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Sheldon (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Siewers (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Simpson (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Stillman - Chamberlain negatives (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Storer (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Stratford, Connecticut - War Memorial (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Union Park Square (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Van Norden (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Van Rensselaer (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Vietor [Victor?] (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Willcox (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Yarnall (Box 10, Folder 31-32)
  - Marine Park, Brooklyn, New York: reproductions of sketches, matted (Box 11)
  - Laucks: photographs, most matted (Box 12)
  - Agnew, Bartram, Bassick, Budd, Casagmo, Hunsaker, Noyes, Yarnall: photographs, some mounted, some oversize (Box 13)
  - Andrews, Bijur, Brown, Crane, Devereauz, Donald, Forsberg, Fowler, Gallaher, Hostetter, Howland, Keating, Lehman, Mallory, Morris, Olcott, Power, Smith, Seift, Van Rensselaer, Wertheim, Zinsser; Butler, Erie, Essex County Golf Course, Gate of Heaven, Loudon Heights, Madison Square, Overview Park; miscellaneous, unidentified photographs, sketches (Box 14)
  - Adams, Anderson, Bowen, Burchard, Chamberlain, Cooper, Cosgrave, Crane, Davis, Dodge, Eton, Florham, Fowler, Gill, Lefevre, Lovett, Mallory, McIntosh, Mitchell, Olcott, Post, Power, Prescott, Smith, Stockly, Storer, Van Rensselaer, Willcox; Battery Park photographs, sketches (Box 15)
  - Unidentified and miscellaneous (Box 16)
  - Charles Downing Lay photograph proofs (Box 17)
  - Schell Lewis Sketches (Box 17)
  - Certificates (Box 17)
    Columbia-Delta Upsilon fraternity; Harvard; National Academy of Design; Olympiade Berlin, 1936; New York City Arts Commission, 1947; American Institute of Planning
  - Student drawings (Box 17)
  - Columbia and Harvard memorabilia (mounted as in an over-sized scrapbook) (Box 17)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 17)
- Series X. Oversize blueprints, sketches, drawings, paintings and photographs
  - Oil Painting, 1912-10-09 (Box 19)
    Lane, Alice Lay
  - Oil Painting Children, 1914-10-10 (Box 19)
  - Watercolours and Etchings, 1924-10-10-1930 (Box 19)
  - School of Architecture 1900 class photograph, 1900 (Box 19)
  - Bassick, Jr.; Bowen and Ives; Davis; Hunsaker; Kraushaar; Laucks (Folder 1)
  - May; Mogul; Pagenstecher; Power; Stockley; Yarnall (Folder 2)
  - Beaver Park; Bridgford Park; Central Park; North End Junior High School; Prospect Park; Woodruff Park (Folder 3)
  - Four-story house; Water color or ink wash, 1899; "Plan for a Small House"; "House for Mrs. C.D. Lay" (Folder 4)
  - Blueprints for Marine Park (Folder 5-6)
  - St. Nicholas Houses, Manhattan, New York (Folder 7)
  - Stratford, Connecticut - blueprints (Folder 8)
  - Coney Island (New York City Fair); Recreation Terraces & Public Baths, 1943 (Folder 9)
  - Mrs. Edgar W. Bassick (Folder 10)
  - Battery Park; Sheepshead Bay Houses (Folder 11)
  - Recreation Terraces and Public Baths (Folder 12)
  - Topographic maps of various properties, blue prints, planting plans, 1900-1930 (Folder 13)
- Series XI. Other
  - Notes, photos, etc. (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Clubs and certificates, 1913-1940 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Lectures by C.D. Lay, Undated (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Century club - membership, 1911-1932 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Century Association - Chateau in Spain, photos and correspondence, 1920-1930 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Century Association - Frescoes, 1922-1930 (Box 18, Folder 9)